outback-australia-travel-secrets.com 2019-05-09

# Outback-Australia-Travel-Secrets.com Privacy Policy

My name is Birgit Bradtke, I own and operate Outback-Australia-Travel-Secrets.com.

I am dedicated to protecting your data and privacy.

I recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information I receive and collect when you use Outback-Australia-Travel-Secrets.com, as well as some of the steps I take to safeguard that information. This will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with me.

I strive to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in everything I do. Likewise, I am dedicated to protecting my online visitors' privacy on Outback-Australia-Travel-Secrets.com.

## About Cookies  

A cookie is a string of information that Outback-Australia-Travel-Secrets.com stores on your computer, which your browser provides to Outback-Australia-Travel-Secrets.com each time you return to the site. I use cookies to help me identify and track visitors, their use of my website, and their website access preferences.  

#### Google Analytics Cookies  

Outback-Australia-Travel-Secrets.com uses Google Analytics to analyze the use of this website. Google Analytics collects demographic and interest data, and generates statistical and other information about website use, by means of cookies. These cookies are kept on your computer. I share this information with Google, which will store and use this information on its servers. Google's privacy policy is available at: <https://policies.google.com/privacy>

I use information from Google Analytics to track the number of visits to Outback-Australia-Travel-Secrets.com, browsers and operating systems. No personally identifiable information is obtained from these cookies. I use the information that Google Analytics generates relating to my website to create reports about how visitors use my website. These reports help me to update the site and improve your usage of it.

If you do not wish your data to be collected via Google Analytics, you can install its opt-out browser extension or add-on which is available here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>

#### Advertising Cookies   

#### Affiliate Products and Services  

#### Refusing Cookies  

You can set your browser to accept or refuse all cookies automatically, or notify you when a cookie is being requested. Taking this action should not cause a problem with the continued use of my site. Consult the Help section of your browser for guidance on how to refuse all cookies or to notify you when a cookie is requested.

If you choose to refuse Outback-Australia-Travel-Secrets.com's cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the features of the site.

## Personally Identifiable Information  

Outback-Australia-Travel-Secrets.com may collect and use your personal information for the following purposes:  

  * To run and operate my site.
  * To display content on the site correctly.
  * To improve my customer service.
  * To help me respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * To personalize your user experience.
  * To understand how my users as a group use the services and resources provided on my site.
  * To improve my site.
  * To improve my products and services.
  * To run a promotion, contest, survey or other site feature.
  * To send information to you that you agreed to receive about topics I think will be of interest to you.
  * To send periodic emails, which may include electronic newsletters and/or autoresponder series of emails.
  * To respond to your enquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

Outback-Australia-Travel-Secrets.com may collect personally identifiable information from you in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when you visit my site, register on the site, or fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources I make available on my site.

  * If you complete a form, I will require your name and your email address, and I will ask for information relevant to the purpose of the form.
  * If you submit content to me for publication, I will ask for your name and email address. Your name and email address will not be published. However, photos you include with your submission, or details in your submission, may personally identify you.
  * If you request to be notified about comments on any content you submit, or request to be notified when others submit content, I will require your first name and your email address.

You can always refuse to supply personally identifiable information and visit my site anonymously. However, it may prevent you from engaging in certain site-related activities.

  * I also collect each visitor's IP address, which helps me combat spam and fraud. I do not use IP addresses for any other purpose.

If I make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information, I will inform you by placing a notice on my site. I will use personal information received from you for internal purposes only and will not sell it or provide it to third parties.

This site lets you share content with your friends and followers on various social media platforms. Below are links to their respective privacy policies:  

My website contains links to other websites that may be of interest to you. However, once you have used them to leave my site, I do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, I cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information you provide while visiting such sites. These sites are not governed by this privacy statement. Always exercise caution by reviewing the privacy statement of the website in question before continuing to use it.

## Non-personally Identifiable Information  

I may collect non-personally identifiable information about you whenever you interact with my site. Non-personally identifiable information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about your method of connecting to my site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider you used, and other similar information.  

## Children's Privacy Protection  

Outback-Australia-Travel-Secrets.com is directed to adults. It is not directed to children under the age of 16. I operate my site in compliance with current regulations. Anyone under the age of 16 must provide parental consent to use this site. I do not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from anyone under 16 years of age.  

## Release of Information  

If I sell Outback-Australia-Travel-Secrets.com, the information I have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in my site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale so that the service provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through my website of that change in control and practices, and I will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make.  

## Data Storage  

All personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information is stored on my host's servers. That host is SiteSell Inc., located at 1000 Saint-Jean Boulevard, Suite 702 Pointe-Claire, QC H9R 5P1 Canada.

Canada is one of the countries that already  has GDPR compliant standards for data processing in place and is therefore considered secure under the new regulations.  

## How You Can Correct or Remove Information  

I provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of my commitment to protect your personally identifiable information. If you have submitted personally identifiable information through my website and would like to review that information, click on [this link](https://www.outback-australia-travel-secrets.com/gdpr-review.html).

You can also request to edit or delete any of your information from the servers by clicking on [this link](https://www.outback-australia-travel-secrets.com/gdpr-request.html).

## Updates and Effective Date  

Outback-Australia-Travel-Secrets.com reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in my cookie and privacy practices, I will indicate on my site that those practices have changed and provide a link to the updated privacy policy. I encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information I collect and how I use it.  

## Agreeing to Terms  

If you do not agree to Outback-Australia-Travel-Secrets.com's privacy policy as posted here on this website, please do not consent to the setting of cookies and the collection and storage of your personally identifiable information.

Your explicit consent indicates acceptance of this privacy policy in its entirety.

If you have any questions left regarding this policy or how or why I or my partners collect, process and store which data, don't hesitate to [contact me](https://www.outback-australia-travel-secrets.com/contact.html).

Last updated: 25 May 2018

_Return to top_
